JONATHAN E. CHEN INTERACTION DESIGNER

SUMMARY

My name is Jonathan E. Chen, and I'm an <u>interaction designer</u> who codes. I create simple and delightful mobile & web experiences. My ideal design role is a marriage between the esthetic & the functional—a designer who has a hand in bringing his own ideas to life.

SKILLS

ui / ux design (web & mobile)

prototyping with HTML / CSS

tools: Sketch, sass, git, cu terminalproficiency with: Photoshop, Illustrator

• experience with: Rails, Android

EDUCATION <u>Carnegie Mellon University</u>

B.S. in Computer Science, 2009–2012

**Stanford University** 

M.S. in Design, 2015-2017

**EXPERIENCE** 

OpenCurriculum (yc W14)

Product Lead, JAN 2014 - MAR 2014

Helped design a curriculum building tool for teachers; worked on user acquisition and improved user experience of product through extensive research and interviews with local teachers.

verdle

Product Designer, SEP 2013 - DEC 2013

Redesigned existing mobile app for iOS 7; created email templates, brand assets, wireframes, interactive prototypes, userflow maps; conducted user interviews and integrated feedback into process.

PORTFOLIO

• SITE: <u>wikichen.is</u>

DESIGN: <u>dribbble.com/wikichen</u>CODE: <u>github.com/wikichen</u>

CONTACT

I'm currently based in San Francisco, CA.

EMAIL: hello@wikichen.is MOBILE: 909.895.9493

Set in HOEFLER & Co.'s Whitney.